Everything's settled
with Shin Yoo-il's
agency
Don't worry
It feels awkward
seeing you talking
so seriously to me
Ah,
and I'm going to America
America?
Yeah
When are you leaving?
I'll see you off
to the airport
No, you don't need to
I'm not gonna
stay there forever
What?
Hey, don't look at me as if
I'm never coming back
You're coming back
right?
Of course
When I come back
I'll have become
the best director
You're here
Didn't you treat
that wound yet?
Come on in
Hyesung
You know my nickname
is Shindecent
Since I was a trainee
I've been used to people
calling me like that
Groundless rumors
spread everywhere
but I thought
it didn't matter
because I was
reaching to the top
I didn't even
think of myself
as such a good person
But
I'm afraid
you'll get hurt
if you stay next to me